number three asks which of the following
is the best electrophile so whereas a
nucleophile is something that has a lot
of electron excess an electrophile is
something that has an electron
deficiency so it seeks electron density
to coordinate to it electrophile file
meaning love loves electrons wants
electrons to come coordinate to it first
we have butane well there's no
electrophilicity there there is no
region of electron deficiency there's no
partial positive charge there's no
formal positive charge so that doesn't
work B ammonia we do have a positive
charge on that nitrogen because it is
coordinated to four hydrogens but it's
not really going to work as an
electrophile because it cannot
accommodate any more bonds right a
nucleophile cannot coordinate to the
nitrogen it's already coordinatively
saturated it cannot accommodate any more
bonds it's got a full octet so that's
not going to work water of course is not
really